Samuel Folaranmi

Lagos, Lagos, Nigeria



samuel.boye95@yahoo.com



linkedin.com/in/samuel-folaranmi-107074214

Summary

Front-End developer with a proven ability to collaborate effectively with senior developers while spending extra time to be mentored. Enjoy working closely with team members to ensure work is done effectively and efficiently and picking up the slack when necessary. With over 2 years of experience in customer service and satisfaction, I have developed and imbibed a customer-first approach in my code implementations. I'm looking forward to joining a team that helps sharpen my skills and improve my capabilities.

Experience

zuri. Frontend Developer

Zuri Team, Inc.

Jan 2021 - Jun 2021 (6 months)

- ° Led the Front-End team to develop and host a functional website
- ° Collaborated with the Design team in delivering results
- Orked with the Backend Team on integration
- ° Worked with React, Tailwind CSS and HTML5

Cashier

KC Gaming Networks (BET9JA)

Feb 2017 - Apr 2018 (1 year 3 months)

- Interfaced with customers/punters.
- Staked the customers' games on time and avoided errors.
- Handled the customers' complaints on the spot.
- Managed the till and kept a balanced account.

Network Monitor/Customer Service Representative/Tech Support

KKONTech

Aug 2015 - Aug 2016 (1 year 1 month)

- Monitored network uptime and downtime.
- Reported to field engineers on network status and advised them to work on it if need be.
- Made daily reports of customers' network performances.
- Attended to customers' calls and took their complaints.

Education



Federal University Oye-Ekiti

Business Administration - Bsc, Business Administration and Management, General 2017 - 2021



闷 Yaba College of Technology, Yaba, Lagos

Business Administration and Management, Business Administration and Management, General

2012 - 2015

Licenses & Certifications

- (A) Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- S CSS Fundamentals Sololearn #1023-19141
- SHTML Course Sololearn #1014-19141

Skills

Analytical Skills • English • Communication • Information Technology • Front-end Development • JavaScript • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML5 • HTML